{
	"theplotthickens": [
        {
            "Question": "A Black Eye Isnt the End of the World",
            "Answer": "A Book Of Cute Panda Photos And Uplifting Panda Philosophies",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Cat on a Winning Streak",
            "Answer": "A Cat Crawls Into An Actress’s Window And Leads Her To The Scene Of A Murder",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Cat with the Blues",
            "Answer": "A Woman Is Cat-sitting When The Building’s Doorman Turns Up Dead",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Hint of Evil",
            "Answer": "The Archangel Michael Accidentally Chases A Demon Onto Earth",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Nostalgia for Camels",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Essays Describing An Author’s Travels In Postwar Asia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Potato That Wasn’t a Christian",
            "Answer": "A Boy Watches His Mother Cut A Potato, Only To See That It Is Black And Rotten Inside",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Song to Die For",
            "Answer": "A Singer’s Chance At Fame Is Threatened When He Realizes His Band Is Being Targeted By The Mob",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Vision in Velvet",
            "Answer": "Lily’s Pet Pig Disappears, But She Finds A Velvet Cloak That Allows Her To See Visions From The Past",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ai! Pedrito!",
            "Answer": "A Man Discovers That His Exact Look-alike Is A South American Revolutionary Named Pedrito",
        },
        {
            "Question": "ANTIGUA: The Land of Fairies, Wizards and Heroes",
            "Answer": "A Book About A Dragon Who Wants To Eat Everyone, And A King Who Is Determined To Prevent It",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Anybody Can Be Cool But Awesome Takes Practice",
            "Answer": "A Devotional Book For Teenage Christians",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Apocalypse Cow",
            "Answer": "Three Unlikely Heroes Must Save Britain From The Zombie Cows",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Apple Crisp",
            "Answer": "A Gardener At A Magical Museum Falls For An Apple Tree Spirit",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Art and Human Genetics",
            "Answer": "An Advice Book On Finding A Partner Who Complements Your Face So You Can Create Beautiful Children",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Be Bold with Bananas",
            "Answer": "An Early ’70s Cookbook Produced For A New Zealand Banana Company",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Be Your Own Dick",
            "Answer": "A How-to Book On Being Your Own Private Investigator",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Beyond Leaf Raking",
            "Answer": "A Guide For Christian Youth On Volunteering In The Community",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Blueberry Muffins",
            "Answer": "A Police Detective Meets An Elf Who Runs A Shelter For Magical Beings, And A Romance Begins",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Butter Safe Than Sorry",
            "Answer": "A Mystery Novel That Begins With A Woman At The Bank, When Three Armed Amish Men Enter And Start Shooting",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cat Talk",
            "Answer": "An Animal Psychic Gives Tips To Readers Who Want To Better Understand And Communicate With Their Cats",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Catflexing",
            "Answer": "A Guide Book On Weight Training, Aerobics And Stretching Excercises That Require The Assistance Of Your Cat",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Chihuahua of the Baskervilles",
            "Answer": "The Owner Of A Clothing Company For Dogs Claims That Her Chihuahua Has Come Back From The Dead",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Children of the Matrix",
            "Answer": "The Author Of This Book Argues That The World Is Controlled By Unseen Forces That Have Manipulated Humanity For Thousands Of Years",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cobbler’s Knob",
            "Answer": "A Group Of Friends Befriends A Foster Child One Summer At The Beach",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Comma Sutra",
            "Answer": "A Sexy Guide To English Grammar",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cooking with Poo",
            "Answer": "An Award-winning Collection Of Thai Recipes By Chef Khun Poo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dancing Lessons for the Advanced in Age",
            "Answer": "A One-sentence, 100-page Book About An Old Man Who Finds A Group Of Sunbathing Women In The City And Tells Them About His Life",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Diet, Crime and Delinquency",
            "Answer": "How Junk Food And Pollution Can Turn A Normal Brain Into A Criminal Mind",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dinosaurs with Jobs",
            "Answer": "A Coloring Book Full Of Dinosaurs Working Hard To Make A Living",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Does God Ever Speak Through Cats?",
            "Answer": "A Man Moves To Los Angeles And Finds God Through A Stray Cat",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Don’t Let the Pigeon Drive the Bus!",
            "Answer": "A Bus Driver Takes A Break, And A Pigeon Steps In To Take Over",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Don’t Look at Me",
            "Answer": "In This Children’s Book, A Boy Named Patrick Is Called Stupid By His Parents And Classmates, So He Befriends Fluffy The Sheep Who Tells Him He Just Needs To Try Harder",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dragon’s Egg",
            "Answer": "Jack Has A Recurring Erotic Dream About A Dragon Who He Realizes Is Actually Real And Needs Saving",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dreamsnake",
            "Answer": "A Healer Travels Through The Desert Looking For A Replacement Dreamsnake",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Drummer Dick’s Discharge",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Novel About An Honourable Discharge From The British Armed Forces",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Eeeee Eee Eeee",
            "Answer": "A Book About Intelligent Animals Trying To Interact With Confused Humans",
        },
        {
            "Question": "English as a Second F*cking Language",
            "Answer": "A Guidebook To Properly Swearing In English In Order To Succeed In Business And Social Circles",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Enid Blyton’s Gay Story Book",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Children’s Stories",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Extreme Ironing",
            "Answer": "A Book About How Ironing While Rock Climbing, Surfing, Etc. Is The World’s Newest And Biggest Sport",
        },
        {
            "Question": "F U, Penguin",
            "Answer": "Color Photographs Of Cute Animals With Funny Commentary",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Falling to Pieces",
            "Answer": "Two Women Who Are Organizing A Quilt Auction End Up Working Together To Solve A Murder Mystery",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fashion Cats",
            "Answer": "Pictures Of Cats Wearing Outfits Designed By Japan’s #1 Cat Tailor",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fighting the Fuzzy-Wuzzy",
            "Answer": "A Memoir Of A Little Known Victorian Campaign",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fish Who Answer the Telephone",
            "Answer": "Professor Frolov, A Colleague Of Pavlov, Writes Of Animal Experiments In Which Even A Goldfish Can Learn To Respond To Certain Stimuli",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Five Years Hard",
            "Answer": "An Account Of The Fall Of The Fulani Empire",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Flushing and Morbid Blushing",
            "Answer": "A Study Of The Science Of Blushing And Possible Treatments",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Forgive My Fins",
            "Answer": "A Mermaid Princess Tries To Keep Her Fins A Secret From Her Classmates And Teachers In Order To Find A Mate Before She Turns 18",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fuzzy Bones",
            "Answer": "Fuzzy Sapiens Have Recently Been Given The Same Rights As Humans, But Will Humans Ever Accept Fuzzies As More Than Adorable Pets?",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Gadsby",
            "Answer": "A Novel Of Over 50,000 Words That Completely Avoids The Letter ‘e’",
        },
        {
            "Question": "God Is Disappointed in You",
            "Answer": "Basically A Sparknotes Version Of The Bible, In Which Every Story In The Bible Is Told, But Greatly Condensed",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Grandma’s Dead: Breaking Bad News with Baby Animals",
            "Answer": "Perforated Cards To Pass Out That Help You Deliver Bad News With Photos Of Adorable Baby Animals",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Hair in Funny Places",
            "Answer": "A Girl And Her Teddy Bear Discuss Puberty",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Halo",
            "Answer": "An Angel Is Sent To Earth With A Mission, But She Falls In Love With A Human",
        },
        {
            "Question": "How God Gives Us Ice Cream",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Book Committed To Converting Kids To Christianity",
        },
        {
            "Question": "How I Became Stupid",
            "Answer": "A Twenty-something Scholar Is Tired Of Being Brilliant And Aware, So He Vows To Become Stupid Enough To Be Happy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "How to Date a White Woman",
            "Answer": "A Dating Guide For Asian Men Who Want To Understand White Women",
        },
        {
            "Question": "How to Good-bye Depression",
            "Answer": "This Book Argues That Constricting Your Anus 100 Times A Day Is An Effective Way To Treat Depression",
        },
        {
            "Question": "How to Make Money in Your Spare Time",
            "Answer": "A Guide To Making Money Under The Table, With Suggestions Like Joining The Mafia And Dealing Drugs",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Kissed a Dog and I Liked it",
            "Answer": "The Story Of Molly The Dog And How She Brought Love And A Better Understanding Of God Into Her Home",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Told You I Was Sick",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Interesting Tombstone Inscriptions From Around The World",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Want My Foreskin for Giftmas",
            "Answer": "One Man’s Revolution To End Circumcision, With An Illustrated Book About His Search For The Foreskin He Lost At Birth",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Wish I Knew How to Quit You",
            "Answer": "A Book Of Trivia About \”brokeback Mountain\”",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I’d Really Like to Eat a Child",
            "Answer": "A Crocodile Gets Tired Of Eating Bananas, And Decides He’d Rather Eat A Child, But She Fights Him Off By Tickling His Tummy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I’m Barack, Not Borat!",
            "Answer": "A Book Of Blank Pages Featuring A Cover Photo Of Barack Obama With Facial Hair",
        },
        {
            "Question": "If God Loves Me, Why Can’t I Get My Locker Open?",
            "Answer": "A Devotional For Young Christians",
        },
        {
            "Question": "If the Devil Made You Do It, You Blew It!",
            "Answer": "A Christian Devotial For Teenagers On Overcoming Temptation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Immortal Image",
            "Answer": "A Man Must Go Undercover To Stop A Secret Society Of Vampires Who Are Threat To Humanity And Other Vampires",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Iron Eyebrows: A Romance with Too Much Hair",
            "Answer": "A Story About A Woman Who Hates Men With Too Much Body Hair, Until She Falls For A Man With Very Bushy Eyebrows",
        },
        {
            "Question": "It Could Be Verse",
            "Answer": "A Book Of Poetry By The Man Famous For Playing \”king Tut\” In The Original \”batman\” Series",
        },
        {
            "Question": "It’s a Jungle Out There, Jane",
            "Answer": "A Guide To Understanding Men",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Italian Without Words",
            "Answer": "A Guidebook To Communicating In Italian Even If You Can’t Speak A Word Of It",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Jennifer Jean, the Cross-Eyed Queen",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Book About Jennifer, A Girl With Crossed Eyes, Who Is Bullied Until She Convinces Her Parents To Fix Her Eyes So She’ll Fit In",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Jesus in My Golf Cart",
            "Answer": "A Grandmother Decides To Literally Take Jesus Home With Her For A Week To Help Sort Out Her Life",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Jesus Potter Harry Christ",
            "Answer": "A Book About The Strange Relationship Between Harry Potter And Jesus",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Joyful Lays",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Songs Adapted For Sunday School",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Keeping Karma",
            "Answer": "Alex, Who Can Hear What Animals Are Thinking, Meets An Attractive Man With An Injured Fawn",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Knitted Historical Figures",
            "Answer": "A Guide For Creative Knitters With A Collection Of Three-dimensional Figures From History",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Knitting with Dog Hair",
            "Answer": "How To Knit With The Hair Your Dog Sheds Instead Of Using Wool From A Sheep You’ll Never Meet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Kockroach",
            "Answer": "A Cockroach Wakes Up To Discover He’s Become Man",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Let’s Make Mary",
            "Answer": "A 1950s Sort-of Satirical Gentleman’s Guide To The Scientific Seduction Of Women",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ma! There’s Nothing to Do Here!",
            "Answer": "A Rhyming Poetry Book About A Bored Fetus In Its Mother’s Womb",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Macaroni and Freeze",
            "Answer": "A Chef Puts Together A Mac-and-cheese Cook-off Fundraiser For A Collapsed Library Roof, Which Turns Into A Murder Mystery",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Magic America",
            "Answer": "A Story About A Creepy Chemical Plant, Radioactive Cats, And Cocky Fairy Godmothers",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Manga Dogs",
            "Answer": "A Teen Manga Artist Joins Her High School Drawing Class And Is Disappointed To Find A Room Full Of Pretty Boys With No Talent",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Manifold Destiny",
            "Answer": "A Guide To Cooking Food On Your Car Engine",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mayo Chiki 1",
            "Answer": "A Teenager Who Is So Afraid Of Women That Sometimes They Give Him A Nosebleed, Finds Out That His Male Friend Is Actually A Girl",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Memorable Balls",
            "Answer": "A History Of The Most Lavish And Interesting Masquerade Balls Of All Time",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Menace of the Saucers",
            "Answer": "A Sci-fi Writer Witnesses Two Spaceships Fighting To Take Over Earth, But No One Believes Him",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mermaids in Paradise",
            "Answer": "A Couple Of Vacationing Newlyweds Join Forces To Save The Island Mermaids From Having Their Home Turned Into A Theme Park",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Midnight Sins",
            "Answer": "A Dreamy Ranch Owner Is Really Into A Woman Named Cami, But He Might Have Accidentally Killed Her Sister",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Moby-Duck",
            "Answer": "A Man Seeks To Find Out Where All Of The Rubber Ducks That Fell Off A Boat During A Storm Ended Up",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mommy, Is It a Sin to Be Fat?",
            "Answer": "Part Memoir And Part God-centered Approach To Losing Weight",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Morgan and Me",
            "Answer": "A Little Princess Is An Expert Procrastinator, Until She Meets Morgan The Unicorn",
        },
        {
            "Question": "My Beautiful Mommy",
            "Answer": "A Mom Visits Her Plastic Surgeon And Explains To Her Worried Child That She’s Going Under The Knife So She Can Be Prettier",
        },
        {
            "Question": "My Lion Lover",
            "Answer": "Sandra Is An Intern At The San Diego Zoo, Where She Discovers That The Man She Is Studying Under Is Actually Also A Lion",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Natural Harvest",
            "Answer": "A Cookbook Of Semen-based Recipes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "No Cooperation from the Cat",
            "Answer": "Martha’s Cookbook Is Well Underway When Someone Dies And A Cat Helps Her Solve The Mystery",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Nocturne",
            "Answer": "A Woman’s Car Runs Off The Road In Colorado, And She Is Saved By A Handsome Stranger, With Whom She Falls In Love",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Oh My Goddess!, Volume 1",
            "Answer": "A Boy Calls The Goddess Tech Help Line And Is Granted One Wish, And Wishes That The Goddess Would Stay With Him Forever",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Oh, RICK!",
            "Answer": "A Young Girl With A Crush On Her Best Friend Goes To A Weight Loss Camp To Get His Attention",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Oh. My. Gods.",
            "Answer": "A Girl’s Family Moves To Greece During Her Senior Year, Where She Finds That All Of Her New Classmates Are Descendants Of Greek Gods",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Old Dykes I Have Known",
            "Answer": "The History Of A Marshy Region In Eastern England",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Old Tractors and the Men Who Love Them",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Advice Ranging From How To Wash Your Tractor Parts In The Dishwasher, To Saving Your Marriage From Ruin",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Our Occulted History",
            "Answer": "A Researcher Uses Science To Show How Human Civilization May Have Originated With Aliens Who Are Still Here Today, Hidden By The Rich",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pam’s Hot Tub",
            "Answer": "A Cautionary Tale About Eating Too Many Hotdogs Before Getting Into A Jacuzzi",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Panda Ray",
            "Answer": "A Boy And Grandpa Travel In A Time Machine Disguised As A Bathroom",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Papap’s Teeth",
            "Answer": "A Grandfather Stores The Rotting Teeth Of A Vampire In A Box",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Paul Is Undead",
            "Answer": "John Lennon The Zombie Guitarist Kills And Zombifies Paul Mccartney In Hopes Of Reuniting The Beatles And Taking Over The World",
        },
        {
            "Question": "People with Long Ears",
            "Answer": "A Guide To Donkey-keeping With Illustrations And Pictures",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Phone Calls from the Dead",
            "Answer": "A Two-year Investigation Into The Mystery Of Phantom Phone Calls And A New Form Of Psychic Communication",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Piercing the Darkness",
            "Answer": "The True Story Of A Reporter Who Disappeared While Researching New York’s Vampire Culture",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pilates for Riders",
            "Answer": "Pilates To Help Horseback Riders With Alignment And Better Connecting With Their Horses",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pirattitude!",
            "Answer": "From The Creator Of International Talk Like A Pirate Day, A Guidebook On Becoming More Pirate Savvy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Planet of the Knob Heads",
            "Answer": "A Science Fiction Novel About A Robot Who Falls For A Human Girl",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Play with Your Own Marbles",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Advice-filled Stories And Poems For Children",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Please Do Feed the Cat",
            "Answer": "A Cat And His Owner Are Forced To Go On A Crazy Health Diet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pornogami",
            "Answer": "A How-to Book On Crafting Erotic Origami",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Prophets of the Ghost Ants",
            "Answer": "Humans The Size Of Insects Struggle To Fight Off The Ghost Ants",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pus Junkies",
            "Answer": "A Boy With Terrible Acne Is An Outcast, Until His Classmates Find That His Zits Contain A Powerful Hallucinogenic Drug",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Red Lightning",
            "Answer": "A Martian Is Tired Of The Annoying Earth Tourists Who Depend On Gravity, Yet Feels Compelled To Help A Suffering Earth",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Rock’s Hidden Persuader: The Truth About Backmasking",
            "Answer": "A Book That Claims If You Play Many Popular Rock Songs Backwards You’ll Find Hidden Satan Worshipping Messages",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Roll the Bones",
            "Answer": "A History Of Gambling Throughout The Ages",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Sassafras",
            "Answer": "Sassafras The Little Elephant Thinks That Being Sassy Is A Good Thing, But Must Learn Respect",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Satan Burger",
            "Answer": "God Gets Bored With Humanity And Creates A Portal To Allow Aliens Into The World",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Scouting for Boys",
            "Answer": "A Handbook For Teaching Boys About Good Citizenship",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Scouts in Bondage",
            "Answer": "A Professor Engages A Group Of Boy Scouts To Help Dig Up The Remains Of A Chapel, Revealing A Secret Treasure",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Secret Life",
            "Answer": "A Professor’s Study On 60 People Who Claim To Have Been Abducted By Ufos",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Shag the Pony",
            "Answer": "A Story About A Pony Called Shag, Published By The Catholic Truth Society",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Shoeless Joe",
            "Answer": "A Voice Tells A Boy To Build A Baseball Field In The Middle Of His Corn Crop",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Simon",
            "Answer": "Simon, Who Is Trapped In A Wolf’s Body, Falls In Love With Rose, The Only One Who Can Heal Him",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Smells Like Dog",
            "Answer": "A Farm Boy Sets Out To Find His Uncle And The Pirate Treasure, With The Help Of A Droopy Dog",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Sora Nagihara 1",
            "Answer": "A Boy’s Dream Girl Comes To Life From The Pages Of His Manga Book",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Spear of Destiny",
            "Answer": "This Book Explains The Nazi Party’s Rise To Power By Claiming That Hitler Was A Satan Worshiper With A Magical Spear",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Standing Up",
            "Answer": "A Toddler Sees A Statue Of A Boy Peeing, And Decides He Wants To Learn How To Urinate Standing Up",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Stargazer",
            "Answer": "A Story About A Boarding School Exclusively For Vampires",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Starter House",
            "Answer": "A Couple’s Dream Home Seems To Want To Harm Their Unborn Child",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Still Stripping After 25 Years",
            "Answer": "A Guide To Quiltmaking",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Street Boners",
            "Answer": "A Picture Book Filled With Hipsters Of Nyc And Commentary On Their Fashion Sense",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Summer with the Leprechauns: A True Story",
            "Answer": "An Author Recalls Her Encounter With A Leprechaun In Ireland Who Warned Her That Humans Were Hurting The Environment",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tails, You Lose",
            "Answer": "A Woman Loses Her Job As A Tv Psychic, And Volunteers Her Time As An Instructor",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tainaron: Mail from Another City",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Letters Sent Overseas From A City Of Talking Insects",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Taken by the T-Rex",
            "Answer": "A Woman Who Has Never Found A Partner To Satisfy Her Finds Herself Cornered By A T-rex",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Talks with Trees",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Over Thirty Interviews Conducted By A Plant Psychic With Various Trees And Plants",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Taming a Liger",
            "Answer": "A Book For Christians, Filled With Spiritual And Surprising Life Lessons From The Movie \”napoleon Dynamite\”",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Teach a Donkey to Fish",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Book About An Elephant Wearing An American Flag Who Tries To Teach A Hippie Donkey Some Common Sense",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Boy Fancier",
            "Answer": "A Manual For Youth On All Matters Pertaining To Owning Domestic Pets",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Butterfly Kid",
            "Answer": "A Kid Finds A Drug That Makes His Lsd Hallucinations Become Real",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Case of the Musical Cow",
            "Answer": "A Dog Trainer Is Detained By New York Customs",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Day Amanda Came",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Story About A New Girl Who Moves Into The Neighborhood",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Devil’s Cloth",
            "Answer": "A History Of Stripes And Their Use By Religion, Government And Fashion",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Eleven Million Mile High Dancer",
            "Answer": "A Woman And Her Magic Cat Want To Be The First To Journey To Mars",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The English: Are They Human?",
            "Answer": "A Dutchman Tries To Explain The English And Their Quirks",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Fangs of Suet Pudding",
            "Answer": "The Story Of How A Few Frenchmen Fought Against A Group Of Invading Germans",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Fat Man",
            "Answer": "One Of Santa’s Original Elves Is Fired From His Job As Captain Of The Coal Patrol, And Is Very Angry",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Fuchsia Is Now",
            "Answer": "A Girl Gets A Pretty Hat As A Gift And Finds A Magic Fairy Inside",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Girdle of Chastity",
            "Answer": "A Study Of The History Of The Chastity Belt",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Glands of Destiny",
            "Answer": "A Study Of The Role Of The Endocrine Glands In The Formation Of Individual Personality",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Invisible College",
            "Answer": "A Scientist Studies The Influence Of Ufos On The Human Race",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Loneliest Ho in the World",
            "Answer": "Santa Thinks He’s Done Delivering Gifts For The Night, But The Adventure Hasn’t Even Begun",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Loving Dead",
            "Answer": "Two Trader Joe’s Coworkers Are Terrified When People Start Turning Into Zombies At Their House Party, Thanks To A Spreading Zombie Std",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Madam as Entrepreneur",
            "Answer": "A Sociological Analysis Of Prostitution As An Occupation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Mayonnaise Affair",
            "Answer": "A Man Who Is Unhappy With His Life Seeks The Help Of A Plus-sized Prostitute Named Strawberry",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Missionary Position",
            "Answer": "A Book On The Theory And Practice Of Mother Teresa",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Muffin Dragon",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Story Illustrating Simple Economics With A Muffin-munching Dragon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Mystery of the Midget Clown",
            "Answer": "An Illustrated Children’s Book About A Clown Accused Of Stealing A Boy’s Mustache",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The New Radiation Recipe Book",
            "Answer": "A Guidebook From The Late ’60s On Cooking With A The Radiation Brand Gas Cooker",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Princess and the Pony",
            "Answer": "Princess Pinecone Is Taken Aback When She Receives A Short, Farting Pony For Her Birthday",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Relaxed Rabbit",
            "Answer": "A Guidebook For Giving Your Pet Bunny Massages For Better Health",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Sauciest Boy in the Service",
            "Answer": "A Tale Of A Boy’s Rattling Adventure At Sea",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Shadow God",
            "Answer": "Craig Walks Into His Closet And Meets A Shadow God Who Wants To Kill Him",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Snowman",
            "Answer": "A Boy Wakes Up To Find That His Mother Has Disappeared, And There Is A Snowman In The Yard Wearing Her Scarf",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Tenth Life of Mr. Whiskers",
            "Answer": "A Girl Uses A Spell To Bring Back The Cat That She Accidentally Killed",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Troika",
            "Answer": "The Adventures Of An Old Mexican Woman, A Jeep And A Brontosaurus Crossing The Desert",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Underminer",
            "Answer": "A Self-help Book On Dealing With A Best Friend Who Is Attractive, Succesful, And Casually Destroying Your Life",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Things That Go GRR",
            "Answer": "Two Men (one Human And One Werewolf) Find Companionship With One Another",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Thirsty",
            "Answer": "Chris Just Wants To Be A Normal Teenager, But He Seems To Be Turning Into A Vampire",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Ride a Silver Broomstick",
            "Answer": "A Guidebook To Being A Modern-day Witch",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Toilet Baby",
            "Answer": "A Man Accidentally Gets His Toilet Pregnant And Has To Figure Out What To Do With The Resulting Half-human, Half-toilet Baby",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Trawler Boy Dick",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Story Of The Devon Fishing Fleet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Unicorns Are Jerks",
            "Answer": "A Coloring Book Depicting Unicorns In A Variety Of Situations Acting Like Jerks",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Urine Therapy",
            "Answer": "A Book Devoted To Urine Drinking For Health Benefits",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Walter the Farting Dog Farts Again",
            "Answer": "Walter Farts His Way Out Of A Series Of Dangerous Situations And Even Solves A Bank Robbery",
        },
        {
            "Question": "What Bird Did That?",
            "Answer": "A Guide To Identifiying Birds Based On Their Droppings On Your Windshield",
        },
        {
            "Question": "What the Moon is Like",
            "Answer": "An Illustrated Children’s Science Book About The Moon, Written Six Years Before We First Landed On The Moon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "When the Waker Sleeps",
            "Answer": "A Man Takes A Serum That Makes Him Sleep For Fifty Years At A Time, He Wants To Stop It, But Keeps Falling Asleep Again",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Where Willy Went",
            "Answer": "A Little Sperm Named Willy Practices Daily For The Great Swimming Race",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Whippings and Lashings",
            "Answer": "A Girl’s Guide To Knots, Pubished By The Girl Guides Association",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Whitey and Whiskers and Food",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Book About Healthy Nutrition, Featuring A Teacher Who Feeds His Mice Two Very Different Diets",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Who Cares About Elderly People?",
            "Answer": "A Book To Help Kids Understand And Have Respect For The Elderly",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Who Cut the Cheese?",
            "Answer": "A Collection Of Fun Fart Facts",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Whose Bottom Is This?",
            "Answer": "A Children’s Book In Which Children Guess The Animal By Looking At It From Behind",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Why Cats Paint",
            "Answer": "A Photographic Record Of Cat Creativity For Cat Lovers And Art Enthusiasts",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Wild Animus: A Novel",
            "Answer": "A Drug Dealer Graduates From College, Moves To Alaska And Turns Into A Ram",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Your Wood Can Last for Centuries",
            "Answer": "An Informational Book On Forest Protection, Printed By The Us Forest Service",
        }
    ]
}